So I just want to show you how to clean up everything to make sure we don't have any extra cost.
So under demo application, find your user, click on manage access and subscriptions.
Take your user, change it and say unsubscribe and remove.
This will make sure that we're not subscribed anymore.
Just in case the subscription remains even if we delete Amazon Q Business.
Then for your application, just take it and also delete it and type delete.
And this will be late, of course, your Amazon Q Apps as well as your Amazon Q Business.
Here, why? Well, because we're just curious and we were learning together.
So that's it. Now that you've done this, you should not have any cost due to Amazon Q Business in the future.
So I hope you liked it and I will see you in the next lecture.